electricpig.co.uk 2018-10-18

# Privacy Policy | Electricpig

If you’d like to know our policy on all things related to Privacy, you’d better take a look. It makes for right tasty reading!

**Privacy Statement of Republic Publishing Ltd**

**Information about our Organisation and Web site**

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organisation like Republic Publishing Ltd . We are based in UK and our principal activity is online publishing. Our privacy policy covers Republic Publishing Ltd and its Web sites:  
www.ElectricPig.co.uk  
www.republicpublishing.co.uk  
Controller: James Beechinor-Collins

**Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access**

You can access our Web sites home page and browse our sites without disclosing your personal data.

**The services and links of our Web sites**

Our Web sites enable you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data.

Our Web sites do not include links to third party Web service providers.

Our Web sites contain advertising and some contextual affiliate marketing links.

**Cookies**  
You should be aware that by using the site, information and data may be automatically collected through the use of Cookies. 

What are cookies?  
“Cookies” are small text files that store basic information that a web site can use to recognise repeat site visits and, as an example, recall Your name if this has been previously supplied. We may use this information (and share it with third party business partners) to observe your internet use and to compile data in order to improve the Site, target advertising to You and assess general effectiveness of such advertising. Cookies do not attach to Your system or damage Your files. 

What sort of cookies do we use?  
1\. Strictly necessary cookies  
Essential cookies that enable You to browse the site and use its features.  
2\. Functionality cookies  
Cookies that improve the functionality of the site by storing Your preferences.  
3\. Performance cookies  
Cookies that help to improve the site performance and provide You with a better user experience.  
4\. Online behavioural advertising cookies  
Cookies that serve You advertisements, relevant to You and Your interests.

Does anyone else use cookies on the site?  
Third party cookies  
We may also use or allow third parties to serve cookies.  
For example, like many companies, we use Google Analytics to help us monitor site traffic. If we include content from other sites (like Youtube, Facebook, Twitter), You may be sent cookies from these sites. We don’t control them, and You might want to check these third-party sites for more information about their cookies and how to manage them.

How can You manage cookies?  
If You do not want information collected through the use of Cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows You to deny or accept the Cookies feature. Note, however, that “personalised” services may be affected if the Cookies option is disabled. If you wish to disable the setting of Cookies in your browser, please visit [AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=1) for the most up to date instructions.

**Data Collection and Purpose Specification**

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services.

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations.

We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated below.

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose: by indicating in a box at the point on the site where personal data is collected.

**Children’s Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children.

We do not take specific steps to protect the privacy of children who disclose their personal data to us.

We do provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page and wherever we knowingly collect personnal data from children on our Web site.

**Disclosure and Visitor Choice**

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organisations.

Where we disclose your personal data for purposes which are different from those indicated in the table mentioned above, we offer you the opportunity to consent to disclosure:

**Confidentiality / Security**

We do not give visitors to our Web site the option of using a secure transmission method to send us their personal data.

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:

• unauthorised access

• improper use or disclosure

• unauthorised modification

• unlawful destruction or accidental loss

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors’ personal data.

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.

**Access to the personal data we may hold about you**

You can ask us, by sending an [Email](mailto:feedback@electricpig.tv)

whether we are keeping personal data about you.

Upon request, which you can indicate by sending an [Email](mailto:feedback@electricpig.tv)

We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a month. – although we may before require proof of your identity -. We will provide the information without any charge.

We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data:

• erased

• rectified or amended

• completed

We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal.

We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.

**Privacy Compliance**

Our privacy policy is compliant with the following instrument: Data Protection Act

There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organisation.

We cannot demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the privacy instrument.

**Privacy Support**

If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact [ElectricPig.tv](mailto:feedback@electricpig.tv).

We do not recommend another means by which visitors’ concerns may be addressed.

  * [](http://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=Privacy%20Policy%20-%20http://www.electricpig.co.uk/privacy_policy/%20\(via%20@sociablesite\) "Twitter")
  *
